HATRED
UPPER FOUR
You damn slip of a girl...
EPISODE 10:
LOVE HASHIRA MITSURI KANROJI
Hey you!
You've gone too far!
I'm taking Nezuko and Genya
back from you, all right?
Shut up, you shameless tramp!
There's only one person in this world
who can order me around!
"Shameless tramp"?
"Tra..."
Me? You're talking about me?
Unbelievable!
What a foul mouth that boy has!
And he's around the same age and size
as my little brother!
Oh, wait, but demons don't look
their actual age, do they?
Still! What a horrible thing to say!
Crazed Cry of Thunderdeath!
Ms. Kanroji!
Love Breathing...
Third Form...
Catlove Shower!
I'm angry, all right?
I'm not holding back
just because you look like a child!
Holy...
This young girl...
slashed through the attack itself.
I've never seen a sword shaped like that!
It's too fast to follow with the eye!
Is that because of how supple it is?
It's flexible beyond belief!
The swordsmith who forged it is amazing...
but Ms. Kanroji is even more amazing
for being able to wield it!
Love Breathing...
Second Form...
Love Pangs!
Sixth Form...
Catlegged Winds of Love!
She can still keep up even at this speed?
Then, I'll bury her with a spell!
Blood Demon Art...
Countless Striking Trees!
Oh no!
What a wide-ranging spell!
Oh, crap!
The main body's running off!
Can I take on this many of them?
Love Breathing...
Fifth Form...
Swaying Love...
Wildclaw!
Got him!
So fast! But it's no good!
Ms. Kanro—
Is he about to do something?
But I'm good!
As long as I slice off his head...
Ms. Kanroji!
That's not the main body!
It won't die if you cut off its head!
What? No way! For real?
I made the wrong call—
Compressed Sound Waves!
Ms. Kanroji!
Unbelievable!
This girl...
Even after getting hit by that attack,
she's kept her body structure intact!
Did she tense up all of her muscles
just before she got hit?
Nevertheless...
she still shouldn't have been able
to withstand it!
It's baffling!
No, wait.
I see.
This girl's muscular strength...
is a mismatch for her build.
An abnormal constitution!
This is great!
Consuming high-quality flesh
leads directly to power.
But first...
let me pulverize
her skull and brain tissue!
Ms. Kanroji?
No one could ever marry you...
but a bear, a boar or a cow.
The thought of that bizarre hair color...
being passed down to my children
makes me shudder.
Let's forget this marriage interview
ever happened.
Please forget about me.
Farewell.
At 17...
my prospective marriage...
was called off.
Isn't your daddy amazing?
What are you doing? She's just a child!
Mother!
I couldn't flex the muscles
on my thin arms...
Why can't I make one?
but there's a story that my mother
has told me over and over...
about my childhood.
When I was 14 months old...
right when my mother was pregnant
with my little brother...
Mitsuri?
Where are you, Mitsuri?
Mitsu—
Ta-da!
Small child that I was...
I wanted to help her in the kitchen...
and lifted up a 33-pound pickling stone.
Though my mother was renowned
for being unflappable...
that day, she was blown away
for the first time in her life.
Thanks for always being a good helper!
SOBA SHOP
And...
ever since I was a child,
I've had a big appetite.
I loved to eat.
Now, that's a healthy appetite!
Come on, how can you sumo wrestlers
lose to her?
I mean, we hear you...
but man...
Yeah.
There you go!
Sakura rice cakes for dessert!
Thanks, don't mind if I do!
Are you really sure about this?
It's totally fine!
No need to hold back at all!
Hey, you heard him!
Go for it!
Are you ready?
Game on!
Your arms may be thin, Mitsuri...
but the density of your muscles
must be extraordinary!
But...
as I grew older, little by little...
I began to realize
I wasn't like the other girls around me.
Mother, do you think
I can ever become someone's bride?
Why would you ask me that?
Well...
because I'm so strong...
and I eat a lot...
and even my hair color's weird.
You can just stay at home forever, Mitsuri.
But...
women are supposed to get married
and be someone's wife, right?
You can just stay at home forever.
The day my prospective marriage
was called off...
I decided I had to hide it all.
I dyed my hair black.
I stifled my urge to eat.
And I pretended to be weak.
Everyone in my family worried about me.
And then one day...
I met a man who said
he wanted to marry me.
Can I do this?
Can I let this happen?
Am I going to live like this
for the rest of my life?
Eating voraciously...
being strong...
my hair color...
All of that is who I am!
Am I going to pretend
to be someone I'm not?
Isn't there something I can do?
Some way that I can help others
while being me?
Does this mean that there's no place
in this world for me as I am?
Isn't there anyone who will love me?
This isn't right!
It can't be right!
Get up! Get up! Get up!
The next attack's coming!
I know that, all right?
Huh?
Did I black out?
We have to protect Ms. Kanroji!
She has the most potential,
so she's our ray of hope!
As long as she survives...
we can win for sure!
Let's win together!
Nobody's gonna die!
We're all...
How comical.
You're kidding me!
Did I get them?
You guys, thank you!
I'm a Hashira, and I messed up! Sorry!
I'll never let my friends die, okay?
Because the Demon Slayer Corps
is my precious home!
Upper Rank or whatever you are!
It makes no difference to me!
She slashed through it all!
She's so cool!
No way...
will I ever lose to evil people!
Now brace yourself!
I'm going for the kill now!
DEMON SLAYER: KIMETSU NO YAIBA
SWORDSMITH VILLAGE ARC
Splendid.
You're someone the gods have
a special love for...
Mitsuri.
Take pride in your own strength.
All those who speak ill of you...
fear your talent...
and wish they could be you, that's all.
Thank you very much!
Father...
Mother...
Thank you for making me strong from birth!
Everyone in the Demon Slayer Corps
has accepted me!
Congratulations
on being promoted to Hashira!
Yes, congrats!
Oh!
Thanks!
I'm going to give it my all!
Do you want
some sakura rice cakes?
KAKUSHI
Sorry, I only have a few!
The people I protected from demons...
thanked me...
with tears streaming down their faces.
Only a Hashira... Just one strike!
I've gotten rid of the evil demon,
so you're safe now!
Don't worry!
Thank you from the bottom of our hearts!
Thank you!
RESTAURANT
Mr. Iguro gave me some long, striped socks!
Here.
What?
What? What's this?
What's this? Mr. Iguro, what's this?
Take them.
Huh? For me?
Whaaaaat? I'm so happy!
I promise you, I'll treasure them!
No need to treasure them.
No way.
That would be such a waste.
It's fine.
If they get ripped...
I'll give you a new pair.
Okay!
I've wondered to myself...
"Should a girl be this strong?"
Would people...
say yet again that I couldn't be human?
I was afraid...
so I've been holding back my power.
But not anymore!
She's our ray of hope!
Just leave it to me!
I'm going to protect you all, okay?
I'll take care of this one!
So you guys go on ahead
and defeat the main body!
Nezuko!
Genya!
Uh-huh!
DESTROY
I have to increase my heart rate!
I need to speed up my circulation...
to get faster...
and stronger!
More!
DESTROY
You little brats...
HATRED
Didn't I say I was going to protect them?
I'm not letting you go that way!
Tanjiro!
Where's the thing
containing the main body?
Can you spot it?
I can!
Found it!
This way!
While Ms. Kanroji's dealing
with that child demon...
we have to slash the demon's main body
as soon as we can!
This young girl...
She's moving even faster than before!
What did you do?
What are you doing? What on earth—
A mark?
Did she have that from the start?
That...
looks a lot like a demon's crest!
This is beyond annoying!
Thanks to this slip of a girl,
I can't unleash my lizards on those brats!
Despicable!
Nevertheless, it won't last forever.
She's sure to lose stamina!
All humans do!
When I say I won't let you go...
I mean I won't let you go!
That's it!
It's inside that tree!
There's no doubt in my mind!
The demon's inside that tree!
Let's catch up to it!
Almost there!
Stop, you bastard!
Don't let it shake you off!
Hang tight!
Before the tree-thing...
Before that snake-lizard thing...
comes this way!
While Ms. Kanroji's stopping it
from attacking!
I can't even swing my sword like this!
So...
all I can do is this!
Whoa! He's biting it!
His teeth are crazy strong!
But won't that give you an upset stomach?
Genya, are you gonna be okay?
By...
devouring demons...
It's only temporary,
but I can gain demonic traits!
If I consume a strong demon...
it boosts my regenerative abilities...
UPPER FOUR
and increases my muscular strength!
It's down!
Now!
The branches are like whips!
Stand your ground!
Keep moving!
Nezuko's Blood Demon Art!
It's sluggish now thanks to the flames!
It's going to work!
I can do this!
Hinokami Kagura...
Flame Dance!
I still haven't landed a blow
on the demon!
This isn't going to end
until I cut off the main body's head!
Do it! Tanjiro!
It's gone!
It ran off again!
Where'd it go?
It can't have gotten that far!
You bastard!
Don't run away!
Don't run away from your responsibilities!
For every sin you've ever committed!
Every evil deed!
I'm going to make you
pay for everything you've ever done!
You're not getting away, no matter what!
For what you've done...
you're going to take responsibility!
Not anyone else!
You two-faced, shameless liar!
I've never once uttered a lie
ever since the day I was born!
I'm a virtuous weakling!
As pitiful as I am...
nobody shows me any sympathy!
I... I...
I've never lied!
Come on, Nezuko, Genya!
You piece of crap!
Enough is enough...
you stupid moron!
PART 10
Ms. Kanroji, thank you for protecting us.
We're going to defeat
that Upper Rank demon for sure!
Yeah!
Now, it's time for a Taisho-era secret!
Ms. Kanroji says that her hair and eyes
changed to their current color...
after eating 170 sakura rice cakes
a day for eight months!
Is that really true?
In Ms. Kanroji's case,
I can see it happening.
In the first place, there's no way she could
eat that many sakura rice cakes every—
Here, Muichiro!
Ms. Kanroji!
You join me, too, Tanjiro!
Thank you very much!
These are really good!
Next, the final episode...
"A Connected Bond: Daybreak and First Light."
No way are we going to let
some arrogant demon have his way!
That's right.
Let's put up a good fight!
We're so not gonna lose!
TO BE CONTINUED